blockadblock.com 2019-09-03

# BlockAdblock.com Privacy Policy – BlockAdblock

_Last updated: June 2019_  
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for blockadblock.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

  4. This site uses Google Analytics to measure standard site usage metrics.
  5. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**   
**No personally identifiable information is  collected by this website, with the exception of your email address data _which is supplied optionally._**  
Entering your email address on the website constitutes agreement for blockadblock.com to send periodic email updates.  Your email data is stored using a third-party email list management service.  
We do not share email mailing list data with unaffiliated third parties.    
Affiliated parties shall include BlockAdBlock and any other entity that, directly or indirectly through one or more intermediaries, controls or is controlled by BlockAdBlock, or any successor corporation or other legal entity which succeeds as a going concern to all business presently conducted by BlockAdBlock pursuant to a merger, consolidation or sale of all or substantially all of its assets.   
**Your Access to and Control Over Information**   
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by using the unsusbscribe or remove from mailing list feature.

  * Cancel your subscription.
  * Change/correct your mailing list subscription data.

You may also use the contact form to:

  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**    
We do not collect sensitive data such as credit card data. No user data or site data is stored on our server.

**Google Analytics  
**BlockAdblock uses a third-party tool from Google called “Google Analytics” to measure information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, which pages they visit when they do so and what country they come from. BlockAdblock uses the information from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. BlockAdblock does not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by browsing in a private browsing mode or deleting your cookies.

**Updates**  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.  
**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via the Contact form.**
